我刚读到一个实验
I just read about an experiment designed
他们想看看能否在几个小时内
to see if you could make two people fall
让两个人坠入爱河
in love in a matter of hours.
这不太对吧
That doesn't sound right.
我的研究显示 这需要三到五年的
My research has shown that it takes three to five years
厚脸皮和苦苦哀求
of shameless begging.
亲爱的 你这个故事讲出来 我们谁都不好看
Honey, neither of us comes off good in that story.
对 我...
Yeah, I... I...
我看过你说的那篇文章
I saw that article you're talking about.
参与者会相互问一系列问题
Uh, the participants ask each other a series
以增进彼此的亲密度
of questions designed to promote intimacy.
最后则需要
深情对望四分钟
into each other's eyes for four minutes.
那是胡说
Oh, that's nonsense.
我表明了对你的爱
I proclaimed my love for you.
可上次我看着你的眼睛
And the last time I looked into your eyes
还是因为你觉得自己得了结膜炎
was when you thought you had conjunctivitis.
虽说我的确患病了
Other than the fact that I had it,
但那晚真的很棒
that was a magical night.
Raj 你和Emily尝试过类似的实验吗?
Raj, would you ever try an experiment like that with Emily?
什么? 我不需要用科学来应得她的芳心
What? I don't need science to win her heart.
我可以用家产打动她
I have my family's wealth for that.
我是说 你没法在几个小时里创造爱情
I'm telling you, you can't create love in a few hours.
- 对吧?  - 说话小心
- Right?  - Oh, careful.
你这是在质疑"非诚勿扰"的能力
You're poking at the whole foundation of The Bachelor.
没错
Yeah, but
但我们不必争论
we don't have to debate this.
我们是科学家
We're scientists.
可以进行自己的研究
We can conduct our own research.
我提议 我们去抓
Yeah, I propose that we imprison
- 两个路人来  - 不行
- two street people.  - No.
然后...
And...
你都没让我说完
You didn't even let me finish.
- 想都别想!  - 哦!
- Forget it!  - Oh!
你就可以随心所欲在猿类身上做实验
So, you can experiment on all the apes you want.
但我要抓两个人来控制他们的感情
But I want to manipulate the emotions of two captive
你倒觉得我是怪物了
human beings, suddenly I'm the monster.
你为什么
Why don't you
不自己做测试呢?
just do the test?
为了科学事业 我很愿意
In the interest of science, I'd be willing to.
什么? 你竟然同意参与需要你
What? You're okay with an experiment where you have
回答关于心灵深处感受的尴尬问题的实验?
to answer awkward questions about your innermost feelings?
没错
Yes.
拜托 我能和他一起吗? 求你了?!
Please, can I do it with him? Please?!
我听了十年Sheldon的感受了
I've been listening to Sheldon's feelings on things
换你 你上吧
for ten years. Tag, you're it.
那万一实验奏效了呢?
Yeah, but what if the experiment works?
我不会爱上Sheldon的
I'm not gonna fall in love with Sheldon.
我也觉得不会
That's what I said.
在我发现之前 他就偷偷
Before I knew it, he pontificated his way
溜进了我的心里
right into my heart.
趣味知识... "pontificate"
Uh, fun fact... "pontificate"
是由拉丁语里的"pontifex"一词而来
comes from the Latin word "pontifex,"
意为"桥梁建造者"或"教皇"
which means "bridge builder" or "Pope."
爱上了吗?
In love yet?
* 宇宙一度又烫又稠密 *
* Our whole universe was in a hot, dense state *
* 140亿年前终于爆了炸... 等着瞧! *
* Then nearly 14 billion years ago expansion started... Wait! *
* 地球开始降温 *
* The Earth began to cool *
* 自养生物来起哄 穴居人发明工具 *
* The autotrophs began to drool, Neanderthals developed tools *
* 我们建长城 我们建金字塔 *
* We built the Wall We built the pyramids *
* 数学 自然科学 历史 揭开神秘 *
* Math, Science, History, unraveling the mystery *
* 一切由大爆炸开始 *
* That all started with a big bang *
生活大爆炸 第八季第16集
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hdscg.com/==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 酥酥想找人打一架
校对: UU养了只狐狸叫查理
翻译: 忙到爆炸影 黄字君 夏至未寒 奥利奥
我只是好奇问问 Penny
Just out of curiosity, Penny,
如果这个实验真的让我们相爱了
if this experiment does make us fall in love,
你愿意开车送我去威斯康星州日内瓦湖市的
would you drive me to Lake Geneva, Wisconsin
Gary游戏展吗?
for Gary Con?
这是唯一一个纪念
It's the only convention celebrating
"龙与地下城"之父Gary Gygax
the life and work of Gary Gygax,
生平和作品的展会
the co-creator of Dungeons and Dragons.
知道吗?
You know what?
老实说 只要我们相爱了
I can honestly say if we fall in love,
我不仅会开车送你去那儿 那些龙T恤什么的
not only will I drive you there, I will buy you
我也会全买给你
all the dragon T-shirts you want.
好 宝贝 来吧
Okay, babe, let's do this.
Penny和Sheldon做这个实验
You guys are really being calm
你们两个还真是淡定
about Penny and Sheldon doing this thing.
换做是我
If it were me,
我... 会有点小紧张
I... I'd be a little nervous.
- 为什么?  - 是这样
- Why?  - Well,
哪怕这个研究是扯淡
even if the study's nonsense,
我... 并不相信冒险会有好结果
I... I don't believe in tempting fate.
所以我不会去玩显灵板
Same reason I wouldn't use a Ouija board,
也不会挑衅亚洲人
or pick a fight with an Asian guy.
他可能不会空手道 但... 何必冒险呢?
He probably doesn't know karate, but... why risk it?
我觉得我们很安全
I think we're safe.
在高中欺负李小龙的
Well, that's what the bullies
那些家伙也这么想
at Bruce Lee's high school thought.
结果被一拳揍倒!
And then, bam!
空手道
Karate.
他们做实验的时候
Well, are we just gonna
我们就干等着吗?
sit here while they do the experiment?
我们也可以做呀
The two of us could do it.
好啊 应该会很有趣
Yeah, sure, that might be fun.
第一个问题是什么?
What's the first question?
等等
Hang on.
好了
Okay.
"在全世界所有人中
"Given the choice of anyone in the world,
你最想和谁共进晚餐?"
whom would you want as a dinner guest?"
嗯
Hmm.
老实说 我会选Penny
I can honestly say Penny.
噢... 那我就选个保洁员
Oh... then I choose a janitor.
因为我要吐了
'Cause I'm about to throw up.
我热恋着呢
I'm in love.
我们干点别的吧
Let's do something else.
Emily马上就要下班了
Ooh, uh, Emily gets off work soon.
要不我们四个出去玩吧?
Why don't the four of us go out?
好 听上去不错
Okay. Sounds good.
我们应该打电话给Howard和Bernadette吗?
Should we call Howard and Bernadette?
我不知道他们的飞机什么时候到
I don't know what time their plane gets in,
我发个短信给他们吧
but let me, let me shoot them a text.
他说了葬礼的事吗?
Did he say anything about the funeral?
没说什么 但他似乎状态还不错
Not much, but he seemed to be in a pretty good place.
开什么玩笑?!
Are you kidding me?!
你弄丢了我妈的骨灰?!
You lost my mother's ashes?!
不... 我只是说有时候
No, I... I'm just saying that sometimes
行李会被误转
bags are misrouted.
好吧 行 你们把唯一一个
All right, fine. Where did you misroute
爱过我的女人发错到哪里去了?
the only woman who ever loved me?
是第一个... 呃 第一个 我是说第一个
The first... well, first, I meant first.
我需要一些信息
I just need some information.
呃 你们的航班号码是多少?
Uh, what's the flight number?
是816
816.
我真的是想说第一个的
I really did mean first.
别提了
Just drop it.
你能描述一下那个包吗?
And can you describe the bag?
嗯 呃
Um, well,
它 呃 是黑色的
it's, uh, black.
把手上系了一根红色的带子...
There's a red ribbon tied to the handle...
放鞋的那儿放了全世界最棒的妈妈!
The world's greatest mom is in the shoe compartment!
你准备好开始了吗?
You ready to begin?
好了 马上就来
Yup. Be right there.
我想你大概不要葡萄酒吧
I assume you don't want wine.
是的 在操作重型机械的时候
Correct. You're not supposed to drink alcohol
我们是不能喝酒的
when operating heavy machinery.
什么重型机械?
What heavy machinery?
我们开始吧
Let's just start.
呃 作为一个来自德克萨斯州的绅士
Well, as a Texas gentleman,
我想说女士优先
I'm inclined to say ladies first.
但是 我担心这种水平的礼貌和魅力
Although, I'm concerned that level of politeness and charm
可能在实验开始之前就让你爱上我的
might make you fall in love with me before the test even begins.
也许我们应该投硬币
Perhaps we should flip a coin.
或者 如果你对石头剪刀布
Or if you're familiar with the rules
的规则很了解的话...
of Rock, Paper, Scissors...
第一个问题
Question one.
"如果你可以
"Given the choice
"选择这个世界上的任何人 你会邀请谁
"of anyone in the world, whom would you want
和你共进晚餐?"
as a dinner guest?"
嗯
Hmm.
活着的还是去世了的?
Living or dead?
它说"世界上的任何人"
Just says "anyone in the world."
我猜要活着的吧
I guess that means living.
啊 这样也行
Ah, that's just as well.
虽然我想和欧几里得见面...
As much as I'd love to meet Euclid...
他是几何证明的发明者...
inventor of the geometric proof...
他估计会穿着拖鞋 而我在吃晚饭的时候
he probably wore sandals and I cannot
不能看到脚趾
look at toes during dinner.
哦 我知道了!
Oh, I know!
那个我想和他一起共进晚餐的人
The person I'd most like to have dinner with
是我自己
is myself.
你确定你要选这个?
You sure that's your choice?
我对这挺有经验的
'Cause I've had that dinner.
呃 我还没有呢
Well, I haven't.
虽然他们说永远不要和你的偶像见面
And while they say never meet your heroes,
但我觉得我不可能会失望
I just don't see how I could disappoint.
你会选谁?
Who would you choose?
- 小罗伯特·唐尼  - 你...
- Robert Downey, Jr.  - You...
哦!
Oh!
我没想到钢铁侠
I didn't think of Iron Man.
其实 也许我和我自己吃好晚饭之后
You know, maybe after myself and I have dinner,
我们可以来和你们两个人一起吃甜点
we can meet you two for dessert.
那你们打算干什么?
So, what do you guys want to do?
呃 我们反正是跟着你们的 你选吧
Well, we're the ones tagging along, you pick.
哦!
Ooh!
你们去玩过密室逃脱吗?
Have you ever been to an escape room?
嗯 那是什么?  - 嗯...
Mm-mm, what's that?  - Um...
它有点像一个互动式的剧院
it's kind of like interactive theater,
你需要在规定时间内
except you have to solve puzzles
解开各种谜题 并逃出房间
in a certain amount of time to get out.
在市中心有一家
There's one downtown where they
他们把你和一个僵尸一起关在房间里
trap you in a room with a zombie.
哦!
Oh!
也就是说有点像现在Penny的情况
So, kind of like what's happening with Penny right now.
"对你来说
"What would constitute
完美的一天需要哪些东西?"
a perfect day for you?"
呃 这...
Uh, well...
我估计会睡个懒觉 做点瑜伽
I'd probably sleep in, do a little yoga,
然后躺在沙滩上
then lie on the beach while
帅气的小哥给我拿饮料...
cute cabana boys brought me drinks and...
也许做个按摩 然后晚上
probably get a massage and then cap off the night
去跳舞
with some dancing.
- 就这些?  - 是啊 怎么了?
- That's it?  - Yeah, why?
你没提到Leonard
You didn't mention Leonard.
他在那
He's there.
我不觉得
I don't think so.
Leonard受不了
Leonard can't stand
瑜伽 海滩 按摩和跳舞
yoga, the beach, massages or dancing.
那他带了一本书 行了吗?
Yeah, well, he brought a book, okay?
- 你的完美一天呢?  - 呃...
- What's yours?  - Yeah...
呃 我醒来
Uh, I wake up.
享受一点法式土司配黄油和糖浆
Uh, I enjoy some French toast with butter and syrup.
呃 然后一个虫洞打开了
Uh, then a wormhole opens,
把我带到了几百万年之后的未来
and whisks me millions of years
我用我极高的智力
into the future where my towering intellect
去拯救被一个噬人的外星种族入侵之后
is used to save the last remnants of mankind
残存的人类
from a predatory alien race.
真有趣 你没有提到Amy
Interesting, you didn't mention Amy.
那你以为法式土司配黄油和糖浆是谁做的?
Who do you think made the French toast with butter and syrup?
你们即将进入
You're about to enter the lab
已故的David Saltzberg博士的实验室
of the late Dr. David Saltzberg.
当他在研究减缓老化进程时
While conducting studies on slowing
发生了一起灾难性的事故
the aging process, there was a catastrophic accident
他死了
and he died.
他真的死了?
Or did he?
女士优先?
Ladies?
你是礼貌还是害怕?
Are you being polite or scared?
是啊
Yup.
啊 这房间真厉害!
Ah, what a room!
- 哦哦!  - 哦!
- Oh-oh!  - Oh!
这真酷
This is cool.
那我们怎么开始?
So, how do we start?
我们需要寻找藏在房间里的线索
We have to look for the clues hidden around the room.
呃 不是应该有一个僵尸吗?
Uh, wasn't there supposed to be a zombie?
哦!
Ooh!
好吧 我希望线索是写在
Okay, let's hope one of the clues
干净的内裤上面
is written on a pair of clean underwear.
Wolowitz夫妇?
Mr. and Mrs. Wolowitz?
据我所知 你们的包裹被运到了洛杉矶
As far as I can tell, your bag arrived in Los Angeles.
那它在哪?
So, where is it?
我不知道 也许某人
I don't know, perhaps somebody
一不小心把它拿走了?
took it off the carousel by mistake?
也就是说 我的妈妈在一个陌生人手里?
So, some stranger has my mom?
你是在跟我说
Is that what you're telling me,
现在我可怜的妈妈在洛杉矶的某个角落?
my poor mother can be anywhere in Los Angeles right now?
我... 我希望我能这么说
I... I wish I was telling you that.
呃...
Um...
那位乘客也可能登上了
But the passenger could've gotten
一架国际航班
on an international flight.
噢 好吧!
Oh, okay, great!
所以 你唯一的工作就是找丢失的行李
So, your entire job is to find lost luggage,
结果你把范围缩小 告诉我
and you've narrowed down the location
我妈在地球上!
of my mother to the planet Earth!
对不起!
I'm sorry!
补偿你们500英里积分可以吗?
W-Would 500 frequent-flyer miles help?
足可以送你们到圣克拉门托了
That could get you to Sacramento.
"如果你明天早上醒来
"If you could wake up tomorrow,
发现自己拥有了一种美德或者能力
having gained any one quality or ability,
它会是什么呢?"
what would it be?"
呃 不是故意想跟圣经学
Well, not to steal from the Bible,
但要是能把水变成酒 那真不错
but turning water into wine sounds pretty good.
你觉得你很不严肃
I don't think you're taking this seriously.
得了吧 我只是和你开个玩笑而已
Come on, I'm just having some fun with you.
我认为
I believe,
你是在用你的幽默
what you're doing is using humor
来掩盖自己的脆弱
to avoid vulnerability.
好吧
Fine.
认真的说...
Honestly...
如果我能有一项美德...
if I could have one quality...
我希望我能向你们一样聪明
I wish I could be as smart as you guys.
哈! 做你的白日梦吧
Ha! Keep dreaming.
Sheldon你!
Sheldon!
对不起
I'm sorry.
我只是和你开个小玩笑罢了
That was me having fun with you.
瞧
Look.
你可能在学术上...
You may not be as...
没我们那么卓越
academically inclined as are we.
对 话是这么说的
Yes, that's how you say it.
但是
But...
你也拥有一个让我妒忌的能力
You possess an intelligence I envy,
这也是我的答案
which leads me to my answer.
我想要一种能力
I would choose the ability
能读懂别人的心思
to read people's minds.
好吧 我读不懂别人的心思
Well, I can't read people's minds.
其实 也不是
Actually, that's not true.
我可以看懂男人的心思
I can read men's minds.
因为通常他们都是同一个想法
But only 'cause it's usually the one thing.
我们什么时候能用上机器眼?
When are we going to get robot eyes?
是啊男人都一样
You're all alike.
好吧 我是想说...
Well, what I meant was...
我总是错误的理解
I often misinterpret
别人的感受
how others are feeling.
比方说 我经常不明白别人只是随意笑一笑呢
Like, I can't always tell if someone is only joking
还是在嘲笑我
or laughing at me.
你知道的 好比说 他们是对我很生气呢
You know, like, uh, if they're mad at something I've done
还是仅仅心情不好
or just in a bad mood.
这... 这总令我压力山大
It... it's incredibly stressful.
真的吗? 你好像总是自信满满啊
Really? You always seem so confident.
呃 我不是的
Well, I'm not.
如果我能看懂别人的心思的话
And if I could read people's minds,
生活就会变得简单多了
life would be so much simpler.
呃 我现在想
Well, now I wish I had
有一种能力去帮你减轻这种烦恼了
the ability to make that stuff easier for you.
谢谢你
Thank you.
哇 我刚刚感觉到了
Wow, I just felt this wave
对你的一股爱意
of affection for you.
你确定你不是喝了太多"果"汁?
You sure it's not too much Bible juice?
现在爱意没了
And the wave is gone.
大脑!
Brains!
安静点! 我们在工作呢
Keep it down! We're working here.
好的 我们解开了密码!
Okay, we've got the cipher decoded!
那个地球仪怎么样了?
How's it going with the globe?
我们正在用坐标定位城市
We used the coordinates to locate the cities.
我正把城市名填到格子里
I'm putting the city names in the grid now.
就能得到密码箱的密码
I'm sure that'll give us the code to the safe.
密解的太快了!
Solve puzzle too fast!
慢点!
Slow down!
好的! 得到密码了
Yup! Got the code.
跟你们说...
Just saying...
提前通关不会退钱的!
no refund for finish early!
你确定不想回家吗?
Sure you don't want to go home?
如果行李被找回来 他们会给我们送回去的
When the bag's returned, they'll deliver it to us.
不 没找到她我不会走的
No, I'm not leaving without her.
好吧 我们等
All right, we'll wait.
我可以送她去的
I could've driven her.
什么?
What?
那天她要去佛罗里达
The day she left for Florida.
她问我能不能开车送她去机场
She asked me to drive her to the airport.
我... 我太忙了
I... I was too busy.
然后...
And...
我给她叫了一辆出租车
I made her take a cab.
我太忙了
I was too busy.
你当时又不知道
There's no way you could've known.
等我一下
Be right back.
打扰一下?
Excuse me?
嗯?
Yes?
你最好把我丈夫的妈妈找到
You better find my husband's mother,
不管是谁
cause one way or another,
反正我们要带个死人出机场!
we're walking out of this airport with a dead woman!
我们要找哪一本书? 呃...
Which book are we looking for? Uh...
物种起源
Origin of Species.
在这儿
Here it is.
这里有个紫外线灯
There's a black light.
噢 等一下
Oh, hang on.
好的
Oh, okay.
呃 "我没有兄弟姐妹
Uh, "Brothers and sisters
但这个人的父亲
I have none, but this man's father
是我父亲的儿子 那么我是谁?"
is my father's son. Who am I looking at?"
行了 我们知道了... 你想吃大脑 安静点
Yeah, yeah, we get it... you want brains. Calm down.
呃 如果我没有兄弟
Well, if I don't have a brother,
那么我父亲的儿子就是我
my father's son is me.
如果我是这人的父亲 那他就是我儿子
And if I'm this man's father, then he's my son.
答案就是"儿子"
The answer's "son."
(儿子和太阳发音一致)
噢! 那里有一张太阳的图片
Ooh! There's a picture of the sun over there.
钥匙肯定就在那后面
I bet the key's behind it.
也可能在其他地方!
Could be somewhere else!
噢 拿到钥匙了!
Oh, got the key!
这就是那扇门的钥匙?
So, that's the key to the door?
这就完了?
That's it?
我们为了六分钟的乐子花了200大洋?
We spent $200 on six minutes of fun?
感觉像是你买的那架遥控直升机
It's like when you bought that remote-controlled helicopter,
就这么... 飞走了
and it just... flew away.
真抱歉 各位 还以为谜题会更难解点
Sorry, guys. Really thought the puzzles would be better.
话又说回来 我们确实都有高等学位
Well, to be fair, we do all have advanced degrees.
写评论的时候别忘这一点!
Remember that before you post on Yelp!
"如果你今晚就要死去
"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity
"且不能与人交流
"to communicate with anyone,
你最后悔没告诉别人什么?"
what would you most regret not having told someone?"
也就是今天吗?
So, it would be today?
哈
Huh.
我觉得能在生日当天死去
Well, I suppose there's something satisfying
也挺满足的
about dying on my birthday.
今天是你的生日?
Today's your birthday?
是啊
Yes.
这可一直是个秘密啊!
Well, that's always been a secret!
连Amy都不知道!
Not even Amy knows!
我不喜欢收礼
Well, I don't enjoy presents.
还有光是想想大家
And the thought of people
跳出来大喊"没想到吧!" 就让人
jumping out and yelling "Surprise!" fills me
心生恐惧 甚至比听到
with more dread than the words
"乔治·卢卡斯导演剪辑版"还可怕
"George Lucas Director's Cut."
乔治·卢卡斯 "星球大战"导演
那你为什么还是告诉了我?
So, why did you finally tell me?
这个实验要的就是
The point of the experiment is
对彼此完全坦白
to be completely honest with each other.
谢谢与我分享此事
Well, thank you for sharing it with me.
我不会说出去的
I won't tell anyone.
谢谢你
Thank you.
说来好笑
That is so funny.
我怎么都觉得你不像双鱼座的
I never would have pegged you for a Pisces.
你现在这样让人很难喜欢你
You're making it difficult to love you right now.
好消息! 您的包还回来了
Great news! Your bag was returned.
谢天谢地!
Oh, thank God!
没事了 她在这呢!
It's okay, she's here!
老妈在这
Ma's here.
那好 多谢你了
Okay, thank you so much.
妈?
Ma?
真抱歉 我没有
I'm sorry I didn't
送你去机场 我只想让你知道
take you to the airport. I just want you to know
我不会原谅自己的自私的
that I'll never forgive myself for being so selfish.
并且我承诺
And I promise
会用我的余生
to keep you close
时刻守护着你
for the rest of my life.
惨了 那东西会放我卧室里了
Oh, no. That thing's gonna end up in my bedroom.
好了! 问题全问完了
That's it! We're done with the questions.
接下来就只要
All that's left to do is
凝视对方四分钟
stare into each other's eyes
并且不能说话
for four minutes without talking.
好的 等等!
Okay. Wait, hang on!
检查尿意
Bladder check.
可以开始了
We're good to go.
准备好了?
You ready?
是的
Yes.
开始
And begin.
感觉有点诡异
This is kind of creepy.
这部分不该说话的
We're not supposed to talk during this part.
抱歉
Sorry.
感觉是有点诡异
This is kind of creepy.
要停下来吗?
Do you want to stop?
我知道你不习惯与人对视
I know you have trouble with eye contact.
你左边的虹膜里
Well, you have a brown fleck
有个褐斑 看起来像是辆
in your right iris that looks
F1赛车
like a Formula One race car.
于是... 我盯着那就好了
So... I'm just concentrating on that.
再就是 盯着我习惯的人会简单点
Plus, it's easier around people that I'm comfortable with.
嗷 小甜心 我也很习惯跟你待一起
Aw, sweetie, I'm comfortable around you, too.
那是自然 我又暖又安心
Of course you are, I'm warm and soothing.
整个人就像碗番茄汤
I'm like a human bowl of tomato soup.
我是说像个小弟弟
I meant more like a little brother.
哦
Oh.
我觉得我是有点把你当姐姐了
Well, I suppose I do think of you as a sister.
甚至有时候 当妈妈
And sometimes, a mother.
感觉又惊悚起来了
It's getting creepy again.
怎么了?
What?
我只是在想
Just thinking about the day
遇见你和Leonard的那天
I met you and Leonard.
那是在一个周一午后
It was a Monday afternoon.
你跟我们一起吃印度餐
You joined us for Indian food.
你能相信已经整整过了八年了吗?
Can you believe it's been eight years?
是啊 你还在这里蹭吃
Yeah, and you're still eating our food.
我... 想不起哪刻
I... can't remember a time
你们几个没在我身边
you guys weren't in my life.
我可记得很清
I remember it perfectly.
但我有过人的记忆力
But I have an eidetic memory.
你感兴趣的话 我还记得
If you're interested, I also remember
你蹭了我们多少吃的
how much you owe us for the food.
完事
That's it.
也不怎么难嘛
That wasn't so bad.
确实不难
No, it wasn't.
现在来统计下
Uh, now let's tabulate
实验结果吧
the results of the experiment.
好的
Okay.
我觉得可以肯定的是 你没爱上我
I think it's safe to say that you're not in love with me
我也没爱上你
and I'm not in love with you.
还有心理学再次
And psychology has once again
证明了自己是科学里最没用的
proved itself the doofus of the sciences.
或许是吧
Well, maybe.
但我还是很高兴做了测试
But I'm still glad we did it.
我是感觉与你更亲近了
I do feel closer to you.
我也你
And I, you.
没错 话就是这么说的
And yes, that's how you say that.
对了 基于我们新建立的亲密关系
Yeah, so, given our newfound intimacy,
我觉得我们
I'd say we have
得做几个艰难的抉择
some hard choices to make.
比如什么?
Like what?
Gary展... 是坐飞机去还是开车去?
Gary Con... do we fly or drive?
要cos吗?
Do we wear costumes?
要的话...
And if so...
谁来扮Gary?
who gets to be Gary?
谢谢你陪我走回来
Thank you for walking me home.
我只是想确保你平安到家
I just want to make sure you get there safe.
好吧 我到了
Well, this is me.
真是有意思的一晚
It's been a very interesting evening.
的确是啊
It really has.
没想到吧! 啊!
Surprise! Aah!
亏我还把Gary让给你扮了呢!
And after I let you be Gary!